

BIO

Julian is a full stack software engineer from Rosario, Argentina. He has experience with Node.js, MongoDB and AWS as a backend engineer. Julian is a motivated team-player who strives to develop meaningful projects that make a real-world impact. He always enjoys taking on new challenges.

CONTACT INFORMATION



📈 julianepoma@gmail.com



julianpoma.com



/julianpoma



/in/julianpoma



Rosario, Argentina

JULIAN EMANUEL POMA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Node.js Developer at Whyline Inc.

January 2019 - Present

Rosario, Argentina

- Responsible for research, design and implementation of new features, such as a polling and survey module, on the backend servers of the Whyline app which is used by more than 350.000 active users.
- Completed full refactor of aging notifications server backend, using functional design pattern focusing on performance and reliability.
- Early design and experimentation with gRPC to develop a micro-services architecture.
- Member of a team that make use of best practices, such as Scrum, code reviews and git-flow.

Full Stack Web Developer at SGC S.A.

October 2017 - January 2019

Rosario, Argentina

- Designed and developed CRM system to manage customer data, active services, available plans, and billing. Intergrated with other software in use at company.
- Created a responsive interface for technicians to activate new service.
- Worked as sole full stack developer, using Laravel 5 and Vue.js.

Freelance Web Developer

September 2018 - Present

Rosario, Argentina

- Delivered web based app for local soda factory. Provided mangement of customer data and orders as well as tracking deliveries and rented company property.
- Various projects ultizing Node.js, Laravel 5, MongoDB and Angular.js

EDUCATION

Software Engineer at Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

March 2014 - December 2018

Rosario, Argentina

Cambridge English FCE at IATEL

June 2013

Rosario, Argentina

Grade B2

SKILLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Advanced

Node.js, MongoDB, Laravel 5

Proficient

TDD, Scrum, AWS, micro-services, Vue.js, Angular.js

Interests

React.js, Rust, gRPC, distributed systems

LANGUAGES

Spanish: native.

English: fluent, full professional proficiency.